翻译  waterlike
翻译  猪猪
翻译  ~某人
翻译  风吹日落
翻译  木月
翻译  小蟹
翻译  小饭
翻译  某羽
翻译  sakura
翻译  天意
时间轴  粢糕
后期   饿得慌
顾问   老杜
校对   草草
总监  草草
第一季  第九集
纸牌屋
人人影视倾情奉献
敌人进攻  你临阵脱逃
When the enemy attacked, you ran away.
就是叛国
That's treason.
现在你该付出代价了
Now it's time to splatter your brains everywhere.
求你了  求求你  不要杀我
Please! Please, don't kill me!
闭嘴  有点骨气受死吧
Shut up! Die like a man!
可我还有妻有儿
But I have a wife and family.
这就是懦夫的下场
That's what happens to cowards.
嘘  嘘  小点声
Hey, shh, shh, shh! You have to keep it down.
-里面正在开会呢  -对不起
- There's an important meeting going on. - Sorry.
我带你去复印室玩吧
I'll set you up in the copy room.
就不会妨碍别人了
You won't be in the way there.
投票将会势均力敌
This is gonna be a close vote.
你们大多同僚不愿在25个选区
Most of your colleagues are not gonna wanna spend
投入这么多钱
this amount of money in just 25 districts.
尽量先说服他们
Try persuasion first.
要点包含在备忘录里
Talking points are in your packets.
如果想了解更多详情
And if you want more detailed information...
调查  数据  可以联系吉莉安或我本人
research, statistics... you can contact Gillian or myself.
如果要做人情  找道格
And when it comes to doling out favors, talk to Doug.
要是那还不行  直接来找我  彼得
If favors don't work, come to me directly. Peter.
我将在宾州展开竞选活动
I'll be campaigning in Pennsylvania.
这周所有的竞选活动
All my events this week
都安排在流域内的几个郡
will be in counties within the watershed,
我会来应对媒体
so I'll be working the media angle.
如果需要我跟谁电话详谈
But if you need me to get on the phone with anybody,
联系克里斯蒂娜
reach out to Christina.
她会帮我做安排
She'll work it into my schedule.
我有话直说了  弗兰克
I have to say, Frank,
拨款两亿很难博得支持
$200 million is going to be a hard sell.
天然气公司的说客已经开始奋力抵制了
The natural gas lobby's already putting up a big fight.
我们的立足点是提供就业机会
We need to make this about jobs.
但开采行业
But the drilling industry
能比法案提供更多的就业机会
can offer far more jobs than this bill can.
我们的法案并不威胁那些岗位
This bill doesn't threaten those jobs,
它只是确保了开采过程的可靠负责
it just makes sure the drilling is done responsibly.
此外还能增加更多就业机会
It adds more jobs on top of that.
桑科已就改竞选经费跟我谈过了
I've already been approached by Sancorp with reelection funds.
我也是  他们向我提供的资助
I have too. They offered me a donation package
来自八个不同的钻探公司
from eight different drilling companies.
-雷米・丹顿  -是的
- Remy Danton? - Yep.
雷米还找过谁
How many of you been approached by Remy?
我知道很难拒绝金钱
Look, I know it's not easy to turn down money.
但如果让共和党控制了宾州的选区重划
But if the Republicans control redistricting in Pennsylvania,
我们会在下次竞选中失去多数席位
we lose the house next election,
你们也保不住各自委员会的主席身份
and all of you lose your committee chairmanships.
这一仗我们要为彼得打赢
This is a feather that we need in Peter's hat.
法案不通过会危及他的胜算
A loss on this bill endangers his chance of winning,
我们要努力保住多数党的席位
and we are fighting to keep our majority here.
还有疑问吗
Any other concerns?
明天下午四点前拿出第一次计票结果
I want a first vote count by 4:00 tomorrow afternoon.
非常感谢诸位
Thank you all very much.
太残酷了  三天要跑22站
It's brutal. 22 stops in three days.
-只能在车上睡觉了  -哪有时间睡觉
- That's a lot of sleeping on the bus. - No sleeping.
我只能在车里干活儿了
That bus is the only place I can get work done.
98年弗兰西斯也曾去巡回竞选
You know, Francis did a big bus tour in '98,
有一次车下坡时刹车失灵了
and the bus lost its brakes going down a hill,
结果冲进了烟草地里
and we landed in a tobacco field.
他下了车  敲开农民的门
He gets out of the car, knocks on the farmer's door,
写了张支票  赔偿损坏的庄稼
writes a check for all the damaged crops,
还借来了卡车  好赶去下一战的活动
and then borrows his pickup so he doesn't miss the next event.
还挺有意思的
And it was actually fun.
他开车  我坐副驾
He was driving. I was shotgun.
工作人员都坐在平板挂车里
We had the whole staff in the flatbed.
我们还提前十分钟就到了
We actually got there ten minutes early.
我觉得我该在这儿争取选票
I think I should be here to help drum up votes.
小心  议员先生  非常烫
Careful, sir. It's very hot.
你和副总统会引起全国媒体的注意
Look, you and the vice president will get national coverage.
这就有助于我们得票了
That's gonna help us with the count.
我联系过他了  但他没答复我
I reached out to him. He never got back to me.
我都不确定他是否知道法案的要点
I don't know if he even knows the talking points about the bill.
我看吉姆并不想去
I don't think Jim wants to go.
他只是看总统和我的面子
He's doing it as a favor to the president and I,
所以他知不知道要点都无关紧要
so it doesn't matter if he doesn't know the talking points.
人们看到他和气的样子就够了
You know, people wanna see him be folksy, you know?
就迁就他一下  给他几分...
So just humor him. Show him some degree of...
天呐
Oh, my God.
-没事吧  -不是故意的
- Are you okay? - It was an accident.
我们该走了  非常抱歉
Okay, it's time for us to go. I'm so sorry.
没事  用冷水冲一下就好了
It's all right. I just need to run it under some cold water.
我不打算说假话
I'm not going to lie.
我讨厌小孩
I despise children.
我就这么说了
There. I've said it.
你怎么能这样呢
You can't act like that in here.
-你得懂点事  -我知道
- You have to be a big boy. - I know.
彼得  我们真得走了
Peter, we really need to get going.
我们已经因为开会错过了一班飞机
We've already missed one flight because the meeting went over.
我又订了9点25的那班  但是...
I booked us another one at 9:25, but...
我们得送孩子去学校
We have to drop the kids off at school.
这样时间就太紧了
It's going to be really tight.
错过了这趟航班  第一站活动就得取消了
If we miss this plane, we have to cancel our first event.
南茜  能送他们吗
Nancy, can you take them?
我得准备午餐小组会议的备忘录
I've gotta get packets ready for the lunchtime sub-caucuses.
彼得  我很想帮你
Peter, I'd do it,
但我们20分钟后要跟绿色和平会面
but we have a meeting with Greenpeace in 20 minutes.
我需要他们对法案的民意调查
I gotta get their rating on the bill.
他们学校在哪
Where's their school?
康涅狄格街和Q街街角
Connecticut and Q.
-我来送他们吧  -可以吗
- Oh, I can take them. - You sure?
没问题  正好顺路
Yes. It's on the way to my office.
这项流域法案再次证明
This watershed act proves that once again
反资本主义的议程
the anti-capitalist agenda
依然在民主党内盛行
is alive and well in the Democratic party.
让我告诉你到底是怎么回事
Let me show you what's really going on.
这是民主党人在吞下
Here are the democrats eating up all of their
民主党人
环保狂热分子给他们强行灌输的
soft science, "Organically homegrown" propaganda
软科学和"有机自产"理念
that the eco-fanatics are force-feeding them.
而这里  是那些蠢事造成的后果
And over here, at the tail end of all those jackasses,
努力工作的中产阶级
就是美国中产阶级
are middle-class Americans...
那些只想努力工作
people who just want to work hard
靠开采业谋生的人
and rely on jobs in the drilling industry.
彼得・罗素  州长
那这个伪君子呢
And what about the hypocrisy, folks?
彼得・罗素还真敢
Does Peter Russo honestly have the gall
教训我们要净化河流
to lecture us on the purity of our rivers
而他多年来一直用化学品污染自己
when he has been polluting himself with chemicals for years?
他不止吃草  还吸食[大麻]
He's not just been eating grass, he's been smoking it.
这是他六年来发起的唯一一份重要法案
It's the only major bill he's sponsored in six years.
我知道  但报道已经覆盖全国
I know, but they already have national coverage.
你想写什么
What's the angle?
如果法案没通过
If it doesn't pass,
我想他会失去船厂协会的支持
I think he'll lose support from the shipbuilders' association.
失去支持  这不够劲爆
So they lose support. It's not that juicy.
船厂协会是他在费城拉票的重头戏
They're a huge part of his get-out-the-vote effort in Philly.
一般人看不懂的
It sounds like inside baseball.
要是能把票数摆在那儿就清楚明白了
Not if I get the vote count. Black and white numbers.
没人报道这个  但我打给竞选办公室
Nobody has that. But when I called the campaign,
他们口风很紧
they stonewalled me.
党鞭办公室也一样
Same thing in the whip's office.
你那里有认识的人吗
Do you know anyone over there?
安德伍德办公室
In Underwood's office?
不  没有
No, I don't.
一个都不认识
Nobody on staff?
毕竟是你给了我罗素的专访
I just figured because you gave me the Russo profile.
不  不是他们给我的
No, that didn't come from them.
但安德伍德组织了竞选
But Underwood organized the campaign.
抱歉  我不认识那儿的人
I'm sorry. I don't know anybody there.
好吧
Okay.
是我  我有些事要告诉你
Hey, it's me. I just wanted to fill you in on something.
大概晚上10点到家  我家见
I should be back home at 10:00. Meet me there.
-这是萨拉折的  -是青蛙
- Sarah made this one. - It's a frog.
我折了这只  你猜是什么
And I made this one. Can you guess what it is?
-龙虾  -不对  是蝎子
- A lobster? - No. It's a scorpion.
送给你的  谢谢你的天鹅
They're for you. For the ones you gave us.
真漂亮
Aw, they're beautiful.
可你不想带去学校吗
But maybe you should bring them to school, no?
向同学展示一下  或者送给朋友
For show-and-tell? Or give them to your friends.
不  其他孩子只会嘲笑我们
No. The other kids will just make fun of us.
为什么
Why?
学校里人人讨厌我们
Everybody hates us at school.
他们说爸爸是瘾君子  我们是毒宝宝
They say dad's a crackhead and that we're crack babies.
毒宝宝: 吸食可卡因的母亲所生的孩子
我上网查过"毒宝宝"
I looked up "Crack baby" on the computer.
我不长那样
I don't look like that.
他们说爸爸会像艾米・怀恩豪斯那样吸毒致死
Yeah, they say dad's gonna O.D. like Amy Winehouse.
艾米・怀恩豪斯: 英国歌手  2011年死于家中
那就告诉他们
Well, you tell them
你们爸爸已经戒毒了
that your dad doesn't do that kind of thing anymore, right?
我们说了  但没人相信
Yeah, we do, but they don't believe us.
你们试过找老师吗
Did you try going to the teachers?
不能那么做  大家只会更讨厌我们
We can't do that. Everyone will just hate us even more.
不能太在乎别人怎么想  是不是
Well, you can't worry about what other people think, right?
真希望爸爸不竞选州长
I wish dad wasn't running for Governor.
-你之前来过艾伦镇吗  -没有
- You ever been to Allentown before? - I have not.
你觉得这里怎么样
What do you think?
比起纽约  停车容易些
Compared to New York, the parking is easier.
想找好百吉饼就没那么容易了
Finding a decent bagel, not so much.
但我们有奶油干酪
We make up for it with the cream cheese.
-开始吗  -你准备好就开始
- Shall we? - Ready when you are.
你的流域法案
Your watershed bill.
你惹火了共和党  石油业  天然气业
You've ticked off the Republicans, oil, gas...
有时为了做正确的事  难免要惹一些人
Sometimes you gotta upset a few people to do the right thing.
不只是一些人
Not just a few.
希望你法案失败的人加起来可不少
There's a sizable coalition that wants to see your bill fail,
包括民主党内的环保人士
including environmentalists from your own party.
他们认为法案不尽如人意
Don't think the bill does enough.
我们的目的是通过法案
We wanted a passable bill.
所以法案没有太苛刻
That's why we aimed for middle ground...
你真的关心特拉华河吗
Do you actually care about the Delaware river?
我不会发起自己不关心的法案
I don't sponsor legislation I don't care about.
在此之前  你从未发起过任何法案
Until recently, you hadn't sponsored any legislation at all.
我在国会集中精力做
I spent my time in congress focusing on things
对我选民重要的事
that were important to my constituents.
造船厂
The shipyard.
我已经尽可能维持了
Kept it open as long as I could.
好  这算一件事  还有别的吗
Okay. That's one thing. What are the others?
我很乐意一一列举
I'd love to provide you a list
我在国会做过的事
of all the things I've done in congress,
但我们只有15分钟
but we've got 15 minutes...
你的反对者认为你的无作为
Your opponent has linked your inactivity
与你嗜饮纯麦芽酒有关
to your fondness for single-malts.
我对自己的过去很坦诚
I've been very open about my past,
我已经竭尽全力去克服它
and I've done everything I can to overcome it
负责且永远地戒酒了
in a responsible, permanent way.
而且比起威士忌  我更喜欢伏特加
And I preferred vodka to scotch.
你该查清楚了再说
You should get your facts straight.
你的流域法案
Is your watershed act
是不是你为竞选州长
just a ploy to jump into the spotlight
用来增加曝光和政绩的策略
and pad your transcript while you apply for Governor school?
钱是真的
It's real money.
工作是真的
It's real jobs.
等特拉华河呈现50年来
And when the Delaware river is less
未有的清澈
polluted than it's been in 50 years...
我们就能举起一杯真正的河水
it's holding up a real glass of its water
看看它有多干净
and seeing how clear it is.
这就是我巡回竞选的目的
That's what my bus tour is about.
-副总统随后也会加入  -没错
- The vice president is joining you later? - Correct.
他怎么这么久才表示支持
Why has it taken him this long to endorse you?
他觉得我不够格
He didn't think I was worth it.
但他听说《纽约时报》要对我进行单独采访
But then he heard I had a one-on-one with the New York Times,
便立刻决定入伙了
and, boom, he was on board.
这话我可能会登出来
I might print that.
多保留我的原话  少添油加醋
The more of my words, the fewer of yours,
这样对我们都好
the better off we'll both be.
议员先生  如果不是认为你会拖累自己
If I didn't think you were such a liability to yourself, congressman,
我没准会喜欢你
I might even like you.
如果你们的发行量能赶上《华尔街日报》
If your circulation was as high as the Wall Street Journal,
我没准也会喜欢你
I might like you back.
放马过来吧  下一个问题
Hit me. Next question.
我必须得做出反抗  弗兰克
I have to put up a fight, Frank.
告诉他们  这是在浪费钱
Tell them they're wasting their money.
-法案会通过的  -你确定
- It's gonna pass. - Are you sure?
我什么时候失算过
When was the last time I got a count wrong?
你真这么有把握  就不必来打压我们了
If you were certain, you wouldn't be trying to neutralize us.
桑科向来待我不薄
Well, Sancorp has been good to me.
我只是想帮你和他们一个忙  雷米
I'm just trying to do you and them a favor, Remy.
那当初为什么要提议这一法案
Then why propose the legislation in the first place?
你肯定知道他们会反对
You must've known they would oppose it.
法案中的监管限制很少
The regulatory restrictions are minimal.
这关乎大局  弗兰克
There's a bigger battle here, Frank.
桑科反对一切监管举措
Sancorp is against any step toward regulation,
无论力度多小
no matter how small.
罗素这是站错队了
Russo's planted his feet on the wrong side of the fence.
你们给了他对手多少钱
How much are you giving his opponent?
去查联邦竞选委员会的报告
Check the F.E.C. filings.
你们实际给了多少
How much are you actually giving?
这可是价值百亿的产业  弗兰克
This is a ten-billion-dollar industry, Frank.
有的是闲钱
There's money to spend.
如果民主党失掉了宾州
If the democrats lose Pennsylvania,
后果你很清楚
you know what that means.
我们不希望你丢了饭碗
We don't want you to lose leadership,
但这取决于你  不是我们
but that's up to you, not us.
你们和共和党人之间
You don't have the same kind of relationship
可没有和我这般的关系
with the republicans that you have with me.
那我们就顺应改变
Then we'll adapt.
我们都还得算选票  祝你好运
We both have votes to count. Good luck.
去告诉桑科  这是在犯傻
You tell Sancorp they're being foolish.
我不会说的
I'm not gonna do that.
那么你就是在犯傻
Well, then, you're being foolish.
别这样  弗兰克
Come on, Frank.
不要人身攻击
Let's not make this personal.
桑科资金雄厚  我难以匹敌
I can't compete with Sancorp's war chest.
我只能采取不同于他们的策略
My only option is asymmetrical...
逐个击破敌人
to pick off the opposition one by one
就像林中的狙击手
like a sniper in the woods.
总有一天  我的准星会对向雷米
There will come a time to put Remy in my crosshairs,
但现在时机未到
but not right now.
加夫尼那里有句老话
As we used to say in Gaffney,
千万别惹正嚼烟草的人
never slap a man while he's chewing tobacco.
罗素竞选州长  崭新的开始
议员先生  你好
Congressman, how are you?
您百忙之中前来  我深表感谢
I deeply appreciate you taking the time out of your schedule...
汉克  我要吃东西
Hank, I need to eat.
去给我弄份总会三明治  双份培根
See if you can muster up a club sandwich, extra bacon.
真不给面子
Fuck me.
我又买了泰国菜
Thai cuisine again.
绿咖喱是给你的  另一份绿咖喱是我的
The green curry is for you, and the other green curry is for me.
我正要出去呢
I was actually just on my way out.
我给你买了晚饭  你必须得吃
I bought you dinner. You have to eat it.
至少也得看着我吃
Or at the very least, you have to watch me eat mine.
我约见别人  要迟到了
I'm gonna be late to meet someone.
-谁啊  约会吗  -一个朋友
- Who? Like a date? - A friend.
那位给你爆料的神秘炮友
Oh, the mysterious fuck-buddy who you get all of your stories from?
别这么严肃  我逗你玩呢
Lighten up. I was just teasing.
而且我也不会说什么
Not that I would judge.
我也干过这事
We've all done it.
从前为了挖新闻
I used to suck, screw,
我不择手段  谁都敢上
and jerk anything that moved just to get a story.
真的吗  都有谁
Really? Like who?
你也想去试试
You want dish?
不  只是
No. It's just...
本・施罗德竞选参议员时的媒体关系主管
The com director on Ben Schroeder's senate race.
国防部的一个职员
A staffer in the Defense Department.
还有个白宫实习生
My very own White House intern.
他嘴没占着的时候可能说了
He was a real blabbermouth when he wasn't eating me out.
我甚至还跟一名国会议员发生过关系
And I even had a fling with a congressman.
哪个议员
Which one?
告诉我你的  我就跟你说
You tell me yours, and I'll tell you mine.
我没睡过议员
I've never been with any.
少来了  你这么性感
Oh, come on. You're hot.
他们就没人对你有过意思
You're telling me that none of them have come on to you?
没在那个圈子里混过
I haven't really been in those circles.
你现在进圈子了
You are now.
可能我没有那种气质
I guess I don't really give off that vibe.
你是说荡妇气质吗
Oh, you mean the slut vibe?
听着  我现在不那么干了
Look, I don't do that shit anymore.
因为话一传开
'Cause once word got out,
我就四处碰壁  没人拿我当回事
it was like I hit a wall, and nobody took me seriously.
就职场策略而言  给你一点建议
So, a piece of advice as far as career strategies go:
为了一点点地位跟人上床不值得
It's not worth fucking your way to the middle.
用筷子还是叉子
Chopsticks or fork?
你要是走了  我就得吃两份了
Look, if you go, I am gonna have to eat both of these,
弗兰克・安德伍德
那可不好
and that is not cool.
不  我留下跟你一起吃
No. I'll eat with you.
好的
Good.
大概晚半小时到
我从不等人
回家  密查姆
Back home, Meechum.
是
Sir.
弗兰西斯
Francis...
你的手怎么样了
How's your hand?
还好
Fine.
不是该换绷带了吗
You should change the bandage, no?
待会儿
Later.
你不是要晚归吗
I thought you were gonna be out late.
不
No.
-你好像心情不好  -没有
- You seem upset. - I'm not.
-发生了什么事  -没事
- What happened? - Nothing.
你能多说两个字吗
Can I get more than two words out of you?
我只是在放松
I'm just trying to relax.
克莱尔
Claire,
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
佐伊指望我焦躁难安地等她吗
Did Zoe expect me to twiddle my thumbs until her arrival?
我看她是搞错了
Perhaps she's making the mistake
以为她的时间和我的一样宝贵
thinking her time is as valuable as mine.
接近权力让一些人错以为他们拥有权力
Proximity to power deludes some into believing they wield it.
我要把这种错觉扼杀在萌芽中
I put an end to that sort of thinking before it begins.
如果我没记错  上次来坦纳斯维尔时
And if I'm not mistaken, the last time I was in Tannersville,
巴蒂・寇克兰把我拉到一边
Buddy Corcharan pulled me aside
跟我说我这是在浪费时间
and told me I was wasting my time,
因为共和党
because the Republicans
在门罗郡会以压倒性的优势获胜
were gonna sweep Monroe County in a landslide.
巴蒂后来只得吃掉他的帽子和鞋
Well, Buddy had to eat his hat and both his shoes
eat one's hat and shoes  赌输了吃掉帽子和鞋
因为是我以压倒性优势赢得了本郡
when I won the county in a landslide.
而且  他有双大脚
And let me tell you, that man has big feet
头更大  够他好好吃一顿了
and an even bigger head, so that was quite a meal.
我爸爸曾给我讲过一个故事
My daddy used to tell me a story
说在小鸡孵出之前就数有几个的人
about people who count their chickens before they hatched.
不过说实话
Although, to be fair,
他大概根本不知道自己在说什么
he probably didn't know what he was talking about,
因为他是匹兹堡人
because he grew up in Pittsburgh.
我家周围也没有一只母鸡
And I certainly never saw a hen around my house,
除非你把我妈也算上
unless you count my mother.
-要我插手吗  -但是  说正经的...
- Do you want me to do something? - But, seriously,
-不用  让他说  -我很爱这座城市...
- No. Let him talk. - ...I do love this town...
我不觉得他会引你出场
I don't know if he's ever going to introduce you.
因为它仍有拓荒者的气质
Because it still has that frontier spirit.
他会的  给他点时间
He will. Just give him time.
都一小时了
It's been an hour.
我们十分钟前就该去卡本代尔了
We were supposed to leave for Carbondale ten minutes ago.
我不能打断他  他可是副总统
I can't interrupt him. He's the Vice President.
我们又不是在宾州边境上
We're not on the edge of Penn's Woods.
我们得把流域法案的经济发展
We need economic development flowcharts
流程图送交泰瑞・乌麦克办公室
for the watershed bill sent over to Terry Womack's office.
-打印稿  20份  -我就去办
- Hard copies, 20 of them. - I'll do it right away.
瑞秋怎么样了
How's everything going with Rachel?
心情不怎么好
I think she's a little down in the dumps.
上周她找到份服务员的工作
She got a waitressing job last week,
但又被解雇了
and then they let her go.
-为什么  -她不告诉我
- Why? - She wouldn't tell me.
就说老板是个变态
All she said was her boss was a creep.
30分钟前  佐伊给我发了条短信
Thirty minutes ago, I received a text from Zoe.
毫无疑问  她想道歉
She intends to apologize, no doubt.
我尊重她想当面忏悔的意愿
I respect that she wants to atone in person,
尽管她花了16个小时才鼓起勇气
even though it's taken her over 16 hours to build up the courage.
简宁・斯克斯基正在调查彼得・罗素
Janine Skorsky is digging into Peter Russo.
具体什么方面
What in particular?
造船厂协会
The shipbuilders' association.
她要怎么写
She have an angle?
流域法案是对他们失去工作的补偿
The watershed bill is a consolation prize for them losing their jobs.
这话说的有点道理
That's not an unfair assessment.
她认为如果法案没有通过
She thinks if the bill fails to pass,
他就会失去船厂的支持
they'll withdraw support.
推测得有点道理
Not an unfair speculation.
我知道你为他的竞选付出了很多
Well, I know how hard you've been working on his campaign,
想给你提个醒
so I wanted to give you a heads-up.
如果她扩大调查告诉我一声
Well, let me know if she expands her inquiry.
-扩大到哪  -你认为值得说的
- Into what? - Anything you deem worth telling.
我能先给她点甜头吗
Well, can I throw her a bone?
如果我透点消息给她  她可能更肯说
She might be more talkative if I have information for her.
-什么样的甜头  -法案的计票结果
- What sort of bone? - The vote count for the bill.
计票还没出来
I don't have a vote count yet.
下午会有个初步结果
Should have a preliminary one this afternoon.
-你会告诉我吗  -有确实消息就告诉你
- You'll let me know? - As soon as I have something solid.
还有件事
There's one more thing.
昨天晚上...
About last night...
不用道歉
Oh, no need to apologize.
你肯定有个充足的理由
I'm sure you had a very good reason.
是的
I do.
我觉得我们不应该继续了
I think we should end it.
不是公事方面  另一方面
Not professionally, the other thing.
为什么是现在
Why now?
我们的工作关系很好
We have a really good working relationship.
我不想搞得过于复杂
I don't wanna overcomplicate that.
可以
All right.
-你没有意见  -完全没有
- You're okay with it? - Completely.
结束了
It's over.
我们之间的合作不会受到影响
And it won't change things in terms of our arrangement?
当然  我不会为一个成熟的决定而惩罚人
Oh, please. I don't punish people for making adult decisions.
谢谢你  弗兰西斯
Thank you, Francis.
她于我微若尘埃
She was never more than a faint blip on my radar.
我们互相利用
We've served each other's purpose.
她想做个成年人
If she wants to be an adult,
就让她看看离巢之后她能飞多远
let her see how she can fly once she leaves the nest.
-克莱尔  -凯瑟琳
- Claire. - Catherine.
谢谢给我时间
Thank you for fitting me in.
对你和弗兰克我总是有空的
Oh, I can always find time for you and Frank.
我来是因为净水计划
Well, the reason I'm here is the C.W.I. has
有一大批滤水器卡在了南苏丹
a large shipment of water filters stuck in South Sudan,
过去四个月一直放在仓库里
and they've been in storage for the past four months,
就放在那儿  苏丹政府...
just sitting there, and the Sudanese government...
不肯让海关放这批货
Won't release the shipments through customs.
我的助理向我汇报了最新进展
My deputy briefed me on the latest.
好  我知道弗兰西斯
Right. And I know that Francis
不久前也跟你提过
spoke to you about this not too long ago,
但最近国务院没有什么消息
but lately we haven't heard much from the state department,
我就想能不能找你帮忙
so I was wondering if you could help.
我们已经尽力了  克莱尔
We've done our best, Claire.
我调了最有能力的人去处理
I put my top people on this.
苏丹那边就是不给回应
The Sudanese are just not responding.
我们还能做些什么吗
Well, is there anything else we can do?
那可是价值超过二十万的设备
There's over $200,000 worth of equipment.
我也想帮你  我知道这对你有多重要
I wish I could. I know how important this is to you,
但我们即将断绝邦交
but we're about to cut off diplomatic ties.
这是总统直接下达的指令
It's a directive straight from the President.
我们无法继续忽视他们违反人权的行为
We can't ignore their human rights violations anymore.
非正式的途径呢
What about back channels?
一旦断绝邦交  无论正式还是非正式
Well, once we cut ties, I can't contact their government
我都不能联系他们的政府
officially or unofficially.
你能帮我联系上什么人吗
Well, is there someone you could put me in touch with?
抱歉  克莱尔  我无能为力
I'm sorry, Claire. My hands are tied.
我愿意为你和弗兰克上刀山
I would move mountains for you and Frank,
但我已经尽力了
but I've done all I can.
当然
Of course.
-见到你很高兴  -我也是
- Okay. Good to see you. - You too.
议员  这周晚些时候
Congressman, you have a major bill
你将有部重要法案进行投票
going to the floor later this week.
-你有信心它会通过吗  -非常有信心
- Are you optimistic it'll pass? - I'm very optimistic.
《特拉华河流域法案》不仅能保护
The Delaware river watershed Act not only protects
州内大部分淡水资源
large portions of the state's freshwater resources,
还能创造数以千计的工作岗位
it also creates thousands of jobs.
我有信心  国会的同事...
I'm confident that my colleagues on the Hill...
促进就业只有一个办法
There's only one way to create jobs.
我任州长时曾实施过
I did it during my administration.
就是减免小公司的税额
The answer is tax credits for small businesses.
我们要鼓励白手起家的企业家们
You've got to encourage self-starting entrepreneurs
经营新企业
to start new ventures,
-雇佣员工  -具体地
- hire employees... - But specifically,
-关于流域法案  -小公司
- about the watershed act... - Small businesses,
才是解决之道  其他都是在装门面
that's the solution. Everything else is window dressing.
非常感谢各位
Thank you all very much.
谢谢
Thank you.
晚安  副总统先生
Good night, Mr. Vice-President.
你好
Hello.
我想谈谈马修斯
I need to talk about Matthews.
没错  我看过新闻报道了
Yes. I read the press reports.
他没帮上什么忙  是吗
He's not being very helpful, is he?
他害多利少
He's doing more harm than good.
我想让他离开
I want to ask him to leave.
那说出去可不好听
Well, that wouldn't make for a very good story.
那也比让他毁了整个巡回竞选强
It's better than him torpedoing the whole bus tour.
你有和他谈过吗
Have you tried to talk to him?
还没  我想先征求你的意见
No, I wanted to ask your advice first.
也许有办法
Well, maybe there's a way
能不赶他走又让他支持你
to keep him on the tour and inspire his support.
我们的观点存在本质差异
We have fundamentally different views.
你无法改变他的观念
Well, look, you're not going to be able change his ideology,
触动他的心
but dig deeper.
吉姆是个骄傲的人  从骄傲下手
Jim is a proud man. Tap into that pride.
我只想他走人
I just wish he was gone.
做你觉得最合适的事
Well, you do whatever you think best.
但无论决定怎样
But whatever it is you decide,
一定要坚守自己的立场
be firm and stand up for yourself.
至少他会对此有所回应
He'll respond to that at least.
还有需要  再给我打电话
And call me back if you need anything.
他给的理由是什么  你闯祸了吗
What was the reason he gave you? Were you messing up?
没有  领班说我做得很好
No. The head waiter said I was doing a really good job.
他第二天甚至开始让我独自负责餐桌
He even started letting me take my own tables on the second day.
那就是经理  他叫什么
And then the manager... what's his name?
里昂
Leon.
他调戏你了
He propositioned you?
他叫我去他办公室
Called me into his office,
说不能再雇新员工了  甚至是兼职的
said couldn't afford to start taking anyone new on, even part-time.
他把手放在我的膝盖上  说可以有例外
Put his hand on my knee, said he might be able to make an exception.
然后他的手滑向了我的大腿
So he started sliding his hand up my thigh.
我站起来说要回去工作
So I stood up and I tell him I should get back to work.
他说"留下"  解开了自己的皮带
He says, "Stay." He unbuckled his belt.
你做了吗
Did you?
没有  我走出办公室  回去工作
No, I walked out of the office and got back to my tables.
第二天去上班时  他要我回家
Next day, I came into work, told me to go home.
我被辞退了
I was fired.
告诉我餐馆的名字
Tell me the name of the restaurant.
你回家好早
You're home early.
我需要休息下
I needed a breather.
今早我都没吃早饭
I didn't have breakfast this morning.
我过会儿可能还要回去
I might head back in a little while.
投票算得如何
The vote count?
这次得最后才见分晓了
It's going to come down to the wire on this one.
我今天和凯瑟琳・杜兰特谈过了
I spoke to Catherine Durant today.
她无法将那批货运出南苏丹
She's unable to get the shipment out of South Sudan.
是的  我们要断绝一切邦交
Yeah, we're cutting all diplomatic ties.
外事委员会对这事很恼火
Foreign Affairs is up in arms about it.
对  据她说  因此她毫无办法
Yes. Which is why she can't lift a finger, according to her.
总之她是这么说的  你得去和她谈谈
It's what she said anyway. Anyway, I need you to talk to her.
我看那样也没什么用
I don't think that would make any difference.
她不是欠我们的吗  弗兰西斯
I thought she owed us, Francis.
确实  但她能力有限
She does, but there's limits.
她是国务卿
She's Secretary of State.
不能违反外交协议
She can't break diplomatic protocol.
那你能打几个电话吗
Well, can you make some calls?
如果她做不到  我也没办法
If she can't, I can't.
再说我得集中精力在流域法案上
Plus I have to focus on the watershed bill.
我都抽时间来帮你弄法案了
I'm taking time out of my schedule to help you with that.
-因为是你起草的  -因为是你要求的
- Because you drafted it. - Because you asked me.
我不想做这事
I didn't want to do this.
我只求你也能抽一点时间帮我
All I'm asking is that you give me a little bit of your time in return.
我要如何解决一个我无力解决的问题
And how am I supposed to fix a problem I can't fix?
雷米怎么样
What about Remy?
格兰顿-希尔在南苏丹一定有联系人
Glendon Hill must have contacts in South Sudan.
他在投票的事上和我们作对
He's fighting us on the vote.
那完全是两码事
Those are two completely separate issues.
根本就是一回事
They are not.
他帮了你的忙  马上就会来要挟我
He does you a favor, he hangs it over me.
你的意思是我的目标在你的之下吗
So what you're saying is my goals are secondary to yours.
我不是那个意思
That is not what I'm saying.
我觉得根本是你拉不下脸来
I think you don't want to go hat in hand
求你的老部下帮忙
to somebody who used to work for you.
你别一进门就教训我
I will not be lectured to the moment you walk in the door!
我说话算话  给凯瑟琳打了电话
I called Catherine, as promised!
她做不到根本和我毫无关系
Her inability to deliver is not my problem or my fault!
我又控制不了全球格局的改变
I cannot control changing global landscapes!
更不会受迫许下无法履行的诺言
And I will not be cornered into making promises I cannot deliver!
抱歉我冲你发火了
I am sorry I yelled.
我压力很大
I'm under a lot of pressure.
你说得对  是我没想清楚
You're right, I didn't think it through.
我现在真的不能去求雷米
I just can't go to Remy right now.
他已经拉拢了太多我的人
He's poaching too many of my people.
还有两位国会议员
I've got two congressmen
仍然举棋不定
who will not commit.
我本来还指望你能跟他们谈谈
I was hoping you might speak to them.
都是谁
Who?
范德博格和艾布拉姆斯
Vanderburgh and Abrams.
你想让我跟他们说什么
What is it that you want me to say to them?
他们很重视环保
They're big on the environment.
他们觉得那项法案没多大用处
They don't think the bill goes far enough.
他们尊重你的意见
They respect your opinion.
我希望你能逐条讲解一下法案
I wanted you to walk them through the bill step-by-step.
让他们放心  我得说服他们投赞成票
Put them at ease. I need to get them in the yes column.
明天我先跟他们碰面  敲打敲打他们
I meet with them tomorrow. I'll deliver the bruises.
之后你再去安抚一下
You meet with them later and patch them up.
软硬兼施估计能管用
That might just do the trick.
没问题
Of course.
我好像把碗打碎了
I think I broke the bowl.
我们因为石油交易和那边有联系
We have contacts there through our oil interest.
我需要政府的干预
I'm going to need government intervention.
有政府的地方我们就有人脉
Wherever there's a government, we know people.
哪怕只是个不成形政府
Even when there's only the illusion of a government.
你会帮我吗
Will you help me?
我很愿意
I'd like to.
但办这么大事  可是要花钱的
But for something like this, I'm afraid there's a price tag.
净水计划会为桑科做环保认证
The C.W.I. will endorse Sancorp as eco-friendly.
他们可以在任何公关和营销材料上
They can use our logo on any PR
使用我们的标志
or marketing materials you want.
这可不够
We'll need more than that.
他们之前肯为这些捐一百多万
They were willing to donate over a million for that.
那些滤水器只有二十万
These filters are only worth $200,000.
这已经很划算了
I'd say that's a bargain.
可你拒绝了那笔钱
You turned down that offer.
现在形势已经不同了
Landscape has shifted since then.
-流域法案  -没错
- The watershed bill? - That's right.
你要我修改法案吗
You want it amended?
我要你让法案流产
I want you to kill it, the whole thing.
净水计划已经公开支持这项法案了  雷米
C.W.I. has publicly backed the bill, Remy.
明面上的事我不管
What you do publicly is your concern.
先生们  请坐
Gentlemen. Please, have a seat.
我们上次谈话之后你们改主意了吗
So have either of you changed your mind since we last spoke?
我们还没拿定主意  弗兰克
We're still undecided, Frank.
倾向赞成还是反对呢
Leaning one way or the other?
如果国会要注资2.5亿美元
If congress is going to allocate a quarter billion dollars,
我们希望这笔钱能投到
we want to make sure it goes towards a
更有利于环保的...
bill that does more to protect the...
这些我们都谈过了  我了解你们的顾虑
We've been through all that. I know your concerns.
所以如果法案的环保措施不能提高
So if the protection standards don't change,
我们更希望把钱花在更有效的举措上
we would rather see that money spent more effectively elsewhere.
那就是说你们都倾向于反对了
That sounds like you're both leaning no.
我们的要求一直非常明确
We've been very clear about what we're asking.
好吧
Okay.
这个是你  艾布拉姆斯
This is you, Abrams.
这个是你  范德博格
And this is you, Vanderburgh.
这边
And over here...
是大多数民主党成员
is the majority of the Democratic caucus.
你们就站在那边孤军奋战
See, you're over there all by your lonesome.
你们并不介意做害群之马
Now, you don't mind being the black sheep.
你们是左派中的左派
You're the liberal wing of the liberal wing.
多数时候你们怎么投票都行
Most of the time you can vote what you want,
反正法案总能获得通过
we still pass things anyway.
但这次
But this time
你们的票很重要
it does matter.
而你们两个没有考虑到的
And what the two of you aren't taking into account
是处在桌子这端和这端之间的
is between this end of the desk and this end of the desk...
是我
is me.
下面我要说其他曾坐在这里的议员
Now, I'm going to say to you what I say to every congressman
也听我说过的话
that sits where you're sitting now.
投票要顾及你的选区  凭良心
Vote your district. Vote your conscience.
别让我措手不及
Don't surprise me.
而其中最重要的一点
And the most important one of those...
就是别让我措手不及
is don't surprise me.
你们俩明天要和我妻子会面
Now, you're both to meet with my wife tomorrow.
你们要洗耳恭听
And you're to hear her out.
她会逐项解答你们的顾虑
She will go through your concerns point-by-point.
我敢保证  之后
And I am certain after that
你们会做出正确的决定
that the two of you will make the right decision.
你们该走了
This is the part where you leave.
我常发现流血的心[悲天悯人者]
I have often found that bleeding hearts
反而很害怕流血
have a ironic fear of their own blood.
流一滴就会罢工
One drop and they seize up.
不过只要伸出关爱之手  将它按摩复苏
But offer them a caring hand and massage them back to life
它就能很快跳动正确的节奏
and they soon start beating to the right drum.
喂
Hello.
我刚跟艾布拉姆斯和范德博格谈过了
I've just spoken to Abrams and Vanderburgh.
就让他们今晚辗转反侧去吧
Let them toss and turn tonight,
明天就看你的了
but they're all yours tomorrow.
我会联络他们的办公室  约个时间
I'll reach out to their offices and set a time.
谢谢你  克莱尔
Thank you, Claire.
应该的  能帮上忙就好
Of course. Whatever I can do to help.
您点的餐  先生  请慢用
Here you go, sir. Enjoy.
不好意思
Excuse me.
牛排上有根头发
There's a hair on my steak.
真抱歉  先生  在哪里
I am so sorry, sir. Where?
就在这儿
Right there.
我没看到
I don't see it.
你是说我没长眼睛吗
Are you telling me I'm blind?
不是  先生  真对不起
No, sir. I'm so sorry.
-我让厨师...  -你叫什么
- I'll have the kitchen... - What's your name?
斯蒂芬妮
Stephanie.
盘子就放这儿  斯蒂芬妮
You can leave the plate, Stephanie.
我想和你们经理谈谈
I'd like to talk to the manager.
好的  先生  我去叫他
Yes, sir. I'll go get him.
谢谢
Thank you.
晚上好  先生
Good evening, sir.
斯蒂芬妮说您的餐盘里有根头发
Uh, Stephanie tells me there was a hair on your plate.
没有
No.
没有头发
There wasn't any hair.
你叫里昂对吧
Leon, right? That's your name?
是的
Yes.
斯蒂芬妮这小妞很辣是吧
Stephanie is a hot little number, isn't she?
屁股真翘
Nice ass.
你逼她给你吹箫是你雇她之前还是之后
Did you make her blow you before or after you hired her?
先生  请你出去
Sir, I'm going to have to ask you to leave.
-坐下  里昂  -先生  请出去
- Sit down, Leon. - Sir, I want you to go.
-我说了  坐下  -别逼我报警
- I said sit. - Don't make me call the police.
听好了  你要是报警
I'll tell you what. You call the police,
我就向移民局举报
I'll call the department of immigration
你厨房里那四个
about the four undocumented employees
非法移民的雇员
you have working in the kitchen.
这是重罪  里昂
Felony, Leon.
我可能还会提及
And I might also mention
你的女友  她母亲和姨妈
your girlfriend, her mother, and her aunt
也是非法移民
who also undocumented and
而且你为她们支付房租
living in an apartment that you pay for.
你进监狱
Prison time for you,
她们被驱逐出境
deportation for them.
不怎么好  对不对
Not a pretty picture, is it?
我们来谈谈瑞秋・波斯纳
Let's talk about Rachel Posner.
票数多接近
How close is it?
今天应该能敲定最后两票
I should have the last two votes I need committed today.
我只需确保没人反悔
I just want to make sure no one changes their mind.
我现在不能
I'd prefer not to
卷入环境问题之中
get embroiled in environmental issues at this time.
但这个方案也能促进就业
But it's also a jobs-creation package.
它不利于石油和天然气的发展
It's antagonizing oil and gas.
教改法案耗资巨大
We can't afford that sort of battle
政府无力再为这场斗争买单
after all the capital we spent on education.
只要政府公开表示支持就行
All I need is one public statement of support.
我不行  不然让琳达明天去帮你吧
I won't do that. How about you take Linda tomorrow?
把她安排在你办公室
You set her up in your offices.
所有拉票会议和电话
Any meetings or calls you might need to whip up votes,
都交给她办
you got her there.
我没法一整天在国会拉票
Well, I can't afford to spend a whole day lobbying on the Hill.
你有助理
Well, you got deputies.
的确是有
Yes, I do.
你是说隔了十个街区就指挥不动他们了吗
Well, you're telling me you can't manage them from ten blocks away?
当然可以  先生
Of course I can, sir.
-如果实在不方便  -不会不会
- Look, if it's too difficult... - No, no, no.
我们帮你  弗兰克
We'll help you out, Frank.
对不对  琳达
Won't we, Linda?
是的  先失陪
Yes. If you'll just excuse me,
我要去调整下行程
I have a few things to rearrange on my schedule.
还有呢  弗兰克
What else, Frank?
说说博奇在计划什么
Tell me what Birch is up to.
我知道我取消两次了
No, I know I've already canceled twice.
下周开始
They start next week.
宝贝  我在想办法
Sweetie, I'm trying to figure this out.
-琳达  -稍等
- Linda. - Excuse me.
-怎么了  -谢谢你同意帮忙
- Yes? - Just wanted thank you for agreeing to pitch in,
我知道你事务繁忙
I know you have a full plate.
应该的  弗兰克
Of course, Frank.
一切还好吗  听起来...
Is everything all right? It sounds like...
没事  我明天什么时候去
Yes. What time do you want me to come by tomorrow?
我们能谈谈吗
Can we talk?
我等会儿再打给你行吗
Can I just call you back in one second?
我打给你  没错
I will call you. Yes.
琳达  很抱歉总统为难你了
Linda, I am so sorry that the president has forced you into this.
这不是我的本意
It was not my intention.
如果你愿意  我可以给国会...
If you would like, I can talk to congress...
不  不是这个问题
No, it's not that.
是我个人的问题  不用担心
It's... It's a personal matter. Don't worry.
什么问题  或许我能帮忙
Well, what is it? Maybe I can help.
就是...我儿子没考上斯坦福大学
Just... my son didn't get into Stanford.
我明天本来要和教务长会面
I was supposed to meet with the Provost tomorrow
看能不能说服他改变想法
to see if I could get him to change his mind.
我向总统请示过了
I asked the president if I could go,
他都同意了  一定是忘了
and he said yes, but he must have forgotten.
你去吧  总统会理解的
You should go. I'm sure the president will understand.
不行  我不会
No, no. I don't let
因为私人问题影响工作  弗兰克
personal matters get in the way of my job, Frank.
琳达  你不能把生活都晾在一边
Linda, you can't put your entire life on hold.
尤其不能耽误自己的儿子
And certainly not at the expense of your own son.
我已经耽误他了
Well, it has been at the expense of my son.
他落榜是我造成的
It's my fault he didn't get in.
我忙着竞选的事  没空陪他
I was on the campaign and I wasn't there for him.
他的成绩受了影响  申请也...
His grades suffered. His application was...
我没照顾好他  弗兰克
I wasn't there, Frank.
但我想  如果可以
But I figured if I could just
和教务长当面谈谈...
meet with the Provost face to face...
行了  你明天去斯坦福大学
Okay, look, you're going to Stanford tomorrow.
如果你去了我办公室
If you show up at my office,
我不会让你进门  所以想都别想
I won't let you in, so don't even consider it.
弗兰克  总统让我...
Frank, the president wants me to be...
不用告诉他
He doesn't have to know.
我找个排程员给你订张机票
I'm going to have one of my schedulers buy you a ticket.
法案会顺利通过的
The bill will be fine.
弗兰克
Frank.
你不必这样
You don't have to do this.
我们虽有分歧  琳达
We may have our disagreements, Linda,
但不代表我们不能互相照应
but that doesn't mean we can't look out for each other.
告诉孩子你会过去
You tell them you're coming.
试音  试音
Test, test, test.
佐伊  我是纽约转播中心的高级制片戴夫
All right, Zoe. This is Dave, the senior producer in New York.
-4分钟后开始直播  -很好
- We'll go live in four minutes. - Sounds good.
第一个话题是国会
The first topic will be the congressional
秋季会议的议程
agenda for the fall session,
然后聊聊中期预测  最后聚焦到
then we'll move on to the midterms, then we'll wrap it up
彼得・罗素的州长竞选和流域法案
with Peter Russo's race for Governor and his watershed bill.
好的
Okay, great.
我现在关掉你的麦  剩30秒时回来
Taking you off mic until 30 out.
简宁  我得说流域法案的事
Hey, Janine, I have to talk about the watershed bill.
-你有提纲吗  -有  稍等
- Do you have a one-sheet? - Uh, yeah. Hold on.
多谢
Thanks.
计票有消息吗
Any word on the vote count?
没有  我给所有民主党议员都打了电话
Still no luck. I've called every democrat in the house
希望能拼凑出个数字  但没人回应
to cobble together a number, but no one's getting back to me.
那我能说什么
So what can I say?
不确定因素很多  票数胶着
That there's a lot in flux, and it'll be tight.
好的  谢谢
Okay. Thanks.
应该的
Yeah. Sure thing.
弗朗西斯  是我
Hey, Francis, it's me.
回我电话
Call me back.
进来
Yes.
罗素议员急着见您
Congressman Russo. He says it's urgent.
好吧
Fine.
早上好  先生
Good morning, sir.
我想聊聊巡回竞选的事
I'd like to talk about how the tour's going.
去车上聊吧  11点不是有活动吗
Well, let's talk on the bus. Don't we have an event at 11:00?
如果不聊清楚  就没必要做活动了
There won't be any events until we talk.
你一直在抢话
You're hijacking the microphone.
你反对我说的一切
You're contradicting everything I say.
我们得推动流域法案
We need to be promoting the watershed act.
我欣赏你的直率
Well, I appreciate your being so forthright.
告诉你我不欣赏什么吧
Let me tell you what I don't appreciate.
民主党委员会让一个毫无经验的瘾君子
The D.N.C. is running a man with zero track record,
参加竞选  接替我的位置
except for substance abuse, to fill my shoes.
我知道你不想来  先生
I realize you don't want to be here, sir,
但现在看来你在故意破坏我的竞选
but it seems like you're deliberately trying to sabotage my campaign.
尽管有违意愿  我是想挽救它
Despite my better judgment, I'm trying to save it.
我比你了解这州的人  彼得
I know the people of this state better than you, Peter.
他们不想听什么流域
They don't want to hear about watersheds.
他们想听工作的事
They want to hear about jobs.
这周他们两者都得听
Well, this week, they need to hear both.
那我也许该闭嘴站在你旁边
Well, then, maybe I should just stand quietly beside you at the podium
看着你输掉
and watch you lose.
-你觉得我赢不了  是吗  -我不看好
- You don't think I can win, do you? - I'm not optimistic.
你前两次竞选州长都输了
You lost the first two times you ran for Governor.
第三次  没人觉得你有机会
The third time, nobody thought you had a chance.
9月  你落后15个百分点
By September, you were 15 points down.
竞选资金不足
You were out of money.
只得抵押房子贷款
You had to mortgage your own house
来支付员工薪水
just to keep your staff on payroll.
我知道我干了什么  我在场
I'm well aware of what I did. I was there.
我要说的是你并没气馁
My point is you kept going.
你不到20天内走访了67个郡
You hit 67 counties in less than 20 days,
证明所有人都错了
and you proved everyone wrong.
不管你是否看好  这次是我竞选
Like it or not, it's my name on the ticket this time,
我有这个机会  我要证明别人都错了
and I got the shot, and I'm gonna prove everyone wrong.
也包括你  先生  正如你当年
Just like you did. Including you, sir.
我希望你支持我  你不肯也没关系
I would like your support, but if you won't give it, fine.
那也阻止不了我
It won't stop me.
你觉得我来这里容易吗
You think it's easy for me to be here?
我卸任州长时正值全盛时期
I left the Governor's mansion right in my prime.
我去做了副总统
To be what? Vice president.
我以为那是升了一步  但知道吗
I thought that was a step up. But you know what?
我一丁点影响力都没有
I don't have a fucking shred of real influence.
我就像个吉祥物一样到处晃悠
I'm trotted around like a goddamn mascot,
这还是我家乡呢
and this is my home state.
我在给你影响力  先生
I'm offering you influence, sir.
我需要你的指导和专业意见
I'd like your guidance and your expertise.
但如果你不愿提供  那么...
But if that's not on the table, then, well...
恕我直言  副总统先生
With all due respect, Mr. Vice President,
你还是回华盛顿吧
you should head back to Washington.
你丈夫说得很清楚
Your husband was very explicit.
我觉得那是威胁
I would categorize it as a threat.
-他说了什么  -别让他措手不及
- What did he say exactly? - Not to surprise him.
他还让你们
Didn't he also tell you
顾及选区  凭良心了吗
to vote your district and your conscience?
他说了  但那个似乎不那么重要
He did, but those seemed far lower on his priority list.
如果你们有强烈理由
Well, he would never fault you
做自己认为该做的事  他不会怪你们的
if you had a compelling reason to do what you think is right.
我糊涂了  你不是支持法案的吗
I'm confused. Aren't you for this bill?
净水计划公开支持它
C.W.I. Is publicly for it.
就我个人而言  也有同样的疑虑
Privately, I have my doubts for the same reasons you do.
我以为
I was under the impression
我们来是为让你说服我们投赞成票
that we were here so you could persuade us to vote yes.
我没想说服你们做任何事
Oh, I'm not trying to persuade you of anything.
我要说
I will say this:
即使法案不通过也不是世界末日
if the bill fails, it's not the end of the world.
我们随时可以发起新法案
We can always sponsor new legislation.
有更严格的管理标准的法案
You know, something with stricter regulatory standards.
我要问明白  你是说
Just to be clear, you're telling us
你不介意我们投反对票
you don't mind if we vote against the bill.
我只是在说我丈夫会说的
I'm simply saying what my husband would...
投票要凭良心
that you should vote your conscience.
-情况如何  -缺一票
- How are we looking? - We're short a vote.
我刚接到克莱尔的电话
I just got off the phone with Claire.
范德博格和艾布拉姆斯被说服了
Vanderburgh and Abrams are on board.
-确定赞成票吗  -确定
- Those are definite yeses? - Definite.
那就没问题了
We should be good.
怎么了
Yes?
我从昨天就一直在找你了
I've been trying to reach you since yesterday.
我一直在忙着计票
Well, I've been a bit busy counting votes.
你说会给我个数字
You said you'd have a number for me.
你该试试打给我的新闻办公室
Well, you should try my press office.
我试了  但没人回电话
I did. They won't return my calls.
官方说法是票数胶着
Well, the official word is it will be close.
我想知道非官方说法
I'm trying to get the unofficial word.
我现在不能有所偏袒  对吧
Oh, I can't appear to be playing favorites now, can I?
这不是因为那天的事吧
This isn't because of the other day, is it?
哪天的事
What other day?
你说我们可以保持公事往来
You said we'd keep our professional relationship.
公事公办就是这样
Well, this is what professional feels like.
有请美利坚合众国副总统  吉姆・马修斯
The vice president of the United States, Jim Matthews!
谢谢
Thank you.
回到布里斯托感觉真好
It's good to be back in Bristol.
加油  勇士们
Go, warriors!
你们都知道我是个话痨
Now, you all know me. I'm a windbag.
我可以一直说到你们睡着
I can go on until you all fall asleep,
睡八个小时
get eight hours of shut-eye,
醒来后发现我还在说个不停
and wake up to find me still yapping.
对于我左边这位年轻人  我有很多话可说
And there's a lot I could say about this young man to my left.
其实  我对他和他的理念  他的过去
The truth is, I've had a lot of doubts about him and his ideas,
他的年轻时代都多有质疑
about his past, about his youth.
但如果你们还记得
But if you'll remember,
我第一次竞选时你们中许多人也都质疑我
a lot of you had doubts about me the first time I ran.
第二次  第三次也是
And the second and the third.
但在过去这几天
But over the last few days,
和彼得一起在宾州巡回竞选
traveling around the state with Peter,
我必须承认  他征服了我
I have to admit he's won me over.
他很聪明  有活力
He's smart, he's energetic,
最重要的是  他是个斗士
and, most important, he's a fighter.
那辆巴士上写着"崭新的开始"
Now, it says "A fresh start" On that bus over there.
这是真的
And that's the real truth,
因为这位年轻人会带给我们州
because this young man will give our state
一个它亟需的崭新开始
the fresh start it so desperately needs.
女士们先生们  有请下届宾州州长
Ladies and gentlemen, the next Governor of Pennsylvania,
彼得・罗素
Peter Russo.
谢谢  副总统先生
Thank you, Mr. Vice President.
布里斯托你好吗
How's it going, Bristol?
今天我想与你们谈谈经济复苏
Today I'd like to talk to you about economic recovery.
你们很多人都知道
Now, as many of you may be aware,
多亏我的对手花了几百万
mostly because my opponent feels the need
在电视上宣传我的过去
to spend millions of dollars on TV ads about my past,
我对复苏也略知一二
I know a thing or two about recovery.
我在自己的斗争过程中学到了很多
I've learned a great deal through my personal struggles.
我学会了如何利用我的力量和决心
I've learned how to harness my strength and my resolve,
为我效力
make them work for me,
如同多年前  布里斯托的水磨
much the way your Bristol watermills harnessed the power
利用美丽的水獭湾
of your beautiful Otter Creek
和澎湃的特拉华河一样
and the mighty Delaware river years ago.
让我告诉你们特拉华河
Let me tell you how the Delaware river
将如何在接下来几年中重振经济
will reinvigorate your economy for years to come!
苏丹的货物要放行了
We're going to get the shipment out of Sudan.
-太棒了  -大概要几周时间
- That's great. - It might take a few weeks,
但你该开始安排博茨瓦纳的工作了
but I think you should start making arrangements for Botswana,
你要在那里建大本营和仓库
where you're gonna set up base camp and the depot.
写完预算后尽快给我
Just send me a budget as soon as you've got one.
克莱尔  能派别人替我去吗
Claire, is there any way we can send someone in my place?
我以为你想亲自去
I thought you wanted to be on the ground.
我想去  但现在不行
I would, but I can't this time.
为什么
Why not?
我不知道该怎么告诉你
I wasn't sure how to tell you this,
但我怀孕12周了
but I passed the 12-week mark.
你怀孕了
You're expecting.
吉莉安  太棒了  那
Gillian, that's wonderful. That...
什么时候的事  谁是孩子父亲
When did this happen? Who's the father?
我在国外认识的一位无国界医生
There was this guy I met overseas. Doctors without borders.
我们在一起过  后来我走了
We had this thing. Then I left.
但他几个月前回了美国
But he came back to the states a few months ago,
就是那时的事
and that's when it happened.
结果不是很好  但我想要这孩子
Anyway, it didn't end well. But I want to keep the baby.
-他知道吗  -他结婚了
- And does he know? - He's married.
我不该这样  很傻
I shouldn't have. It was stupid.
不必解释
You don't have to explain.
我三月初得请几天假
I'll need some time off at the beginning of march.
没问题
Of course.
我们会派别人去的
And absolutely, we'll send someone else instead.
非常感谢  克莱尔
I appreciate it, Claire.
应该的
Sure.
你要三分熟是吗
You said medium-rare?
有什么需要尽管告诉我
Just, uh, let me know if you guys need anything.
你猜这是谁发来的短信
Who would you guess texted me just now?
我以为她能多坚持几天
I thought she'd last more than a couple days.
-出去吗  -一两个小时就回来
- Going somewhere? - Just for an hour or two.
还有个不肯合作的得去收拾
I got one last holdout to whip.
罗素的法案票数是多少
What's the vote count on Russo's bill?
你不先冲个澡
Oh, don't you wanna shower first
再谈事贬低自己吗
before we dirty ourselves with business?
你走了我再冲澡
I'll shower after you leave.
票数多少
What's the vote count?
你的语气让我不太想说
Your tone doesn't inspire me to be very forthcoming.
光上我还不够吗
Oh, the fuck wasn't enough?
还得要个特别的语气吗
You need a special tone too?
有人早上用酸刷牙了啊
Ooh, someone washed her mouth out with acid this morning.
不管你闹什么别扭
Whatever it is you're grappling with,
我真的毫无兴趣
I am sincerely not interested.
你比我老一倍
You're almost twice my age.
你说你不介意
You said that didn't bother you.
我撒谎了
I lied.
你有女儿的话  岁数都比我大了
If you had a daughter, she'd be older than me.
再过二十年  我还是比你现在要年轻
In 20 years, I'll still be younger than you are now.
我肯定辩不过基本的算数
Well, I can't argue with basic arithmetic.
你不觉得这很恶心吗
You don't find that disgusting?
我觉得你想让我这么想
I think you want me to.
但我一直把这当做
But I've never considered this any more or less
两个成年人之间两厢情愿的交易
than a transaction between two consenting adults.
如果你只想找一个帮你办事的女孩
If you just want the girl who will do your bidding for you,
你已经得到了
you already have that.
为什么上我
Why do you need to fuck me?
我要提醒你
I would remind you
是你先勾引的我
that it was you who initiated our affair,
是你去年冬天敲开我家的门
and it was you who came knocking at my door last winter.
也是我要求停止你我现在的关系
And it was me who asked that we stop what we're doing now.
我尊重了你的要求
Which I respected
直到你今晚打给我  要我过来
until you picked up a phone and asked me to come over tonight.
因为不这样你就什么都不给我
Because you wouldn't give me what I wanted unless I did.
告诉我  你为什么要这样
So tell me, why do you need this?
你似乎并不从中取乐
You don't seem to get any pleasure out of it.
我知道我肯定没有
I know I certainly don't.
我好像每次都能满足你
I seem to always leave you satisfied.
你怎么知道我不是装的
How do you know I'm not faking it?
你是吗
Are you?
这都看不出来不是更说明问题吗
Doesn't it say a lot that you can't tell?
我面对墙站着的时候你在想什么
What do you think about when I'm up against the wall?
一位伟人曾经说过
A great man once said
生活的一切都和性有关
that everything in life is about sex...
除了性本身
Except sex.
性关乎权力
Sex is about power.
你是要一个妓女
So you need a whore,
那你就是皮条客
which makes you a pimp.
我不是皮条客  只是一个非常慷慨的顾客
I'm not a pimp. Just a very generous John.
好  既然我们把关系理清楚了
Fine. As long as we're clear about what this is,
我可以扮演妓女的角色
I can play the whore.
付钱吧
Now pay me.
法案会通过的  我们有两票的优势
The bill will pass. We have it by two votes.
把这消息告诉你朋友斯克斯基小姐吧
You can pass that along to your friend, miss Skorsky.
如果她非得说这些才能安然入睡  那随她吧
If she must say such things in order to sleep at night, so be it.
我偶尔给她一点新闻就能换来她的忠诚
Her loyalty costs me nothing but the occasional crumb of news.
她的仇视对我完全无害
Her hatefulness takes no toll at all.
没人会去补偿一个妓女  只为稍后跟她温存
You don't compensate a working girl so you can cuddle after.
最后一轮投票
Final voting...
去了很多小镇  一些群众真的很棒
A lot of small towns, some really great crowds.
也没有刹车失灵
No buses losing their brakes.
别这样  你什么时候回去
Oh, please now. When do you head back?
明天  我们想在投票后举行新闻发布会
Tomorrow. We wanna do a press conference when all the votes are in.
-与会人员  请投票  -你没事吧
- Members, please cast your votes now. - Are you all right?
我感觉有点恶心  会过去的  我没事
I'm just a little nauseous. It'll pass. I'm okay.
-你说你预产期在3月  -3月14日
- You said you're due in March? - March 14th.
真让人兴奋  晨吐严重吗
It's so exciting. How's the morning sickness?
最困难的部分应该过去了
I think I'm over the hump.
我总想上厕所  想要奇怪的东西
I have to pee all the time. Weird cravings.
再做巡回竞选感觉很好  令人振作
It was good to be on the road again. Invigorating.
我们内部计票的结果不错
Our internals are showing a nice bump in the numbers.
你功不可没啊
You made a big difference.
总统很感谢你  我也是
The president is grateful, and so am I.
这是团队努力的成果
Well, it's a team effort, right?
抱歉  我还没和你太太问好
Excuse me. I have yet to say hello to your better half.
-斯坦福的事怎么样  -我觉得还不错
- How'd it go at Stanford? - Well, I think.
校长是共和党人  所以没怎么寒暄
The Dean's a republican, so there was not a lot of small talk.
但他似乎愿意考虑一下  下周就知道了
But he seemed open to considering it. We'll know more next week.
-太好了  -感谢你帮我一把
- That's terrific. - I appreciate your helping me out.
我什么都没做  谁都会订张机票
Oh, I didn't do anything. Anybody can book a plane ticket.
不是这样的  你帮我打了掩护
That's not true. You covered for me.
我们得去照顾那些重要的事
Well, we have to keep the important things in perspective, right?
别以为这样我就欠你人情了
Don't think it's bought you any favors.
求回报的善举只是伪善
Kindness isn't kindness if you expect a reward.
风云人物来了
The man of the hour!
还不是  票数还没统计完
Not yet. The votes are still coming in.
你怎么投的  我投的赞成票
Hey, how'd you vote? I voted yes.
投票  我就知道我忘了什么
Voting. I knew I forgot something.
交给我们吧
We got this.
喝点葡萄汽水来庆祝一下吧
There's some sparkling grape juice there to celebrate.
-还有30秒  -30秒
- 30 seconds remaining. - 30 seconds.
看上去不错
Looking good.
大家快投票吧
Come on, everyone. Let's go.
大家都在按党派归属投票
Everyone's voting along party lines.
你瞧  这就是齐心协力的结果
See? This is what happens when we all stick together.
美国国会
流域法案
投票表决
赞成    反对
胜利如此简单
This is an easy win for us.
15秒
15 seconds.
-快投票  -10秒
- Vote now. - Ten seconds.
美国国会
流域法案
投票表决
赞成    反对
加油
Come on.
这不可能
This can't be happening.
与会成员  请马上投票
Members, please cast your votes now.
美国国会
流域法案
投票表决
赞成    反对
投票结束
Voting is closed.
4913号法案没有通过
Hr 4913 is defeated.
-道格  -我以为我们赢定了
- Doug. - I thought we had it.
那法案就没戏了
So this means it's dead?
真可惜  我们付出了那么多努力
It's such a shame. All of that hard work.
我要知道谁撒谎了
I wanna know who lied.
■
committee chairmanship
参议院和众议院都有各种下属负责不同工作的委员会
而各委员会的主席则由多数党成员出任
少数党成员最高只能作"ranking member"[副主席]
因此弗兰克动员民主党议员时
提醒他们如果重新划选区令民主党失去多数席位
他们也将相应失去各自在不同委员会中的主席位置
■
教务长是美国大学里最有实权的人
如果校长是董事长  教务长就是CEO  比副校长权力还要大
最后转播议会投票的电视频道是C-SPAN
全称为Cable-Satellite Public Affairs Network
"有线-卫星公共事务电视网"
是美国电视行业自主筹资兴办的公益电视台
没有广告  不盈利  全是政治时事的转播
主要是国会辩论  听证会等直播